One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Zoro vs. Ryuuma and
Chopper's Rage!
He made a hole!
To send the stab flying... it takes a lot of strength.
A draw it seems.
You almost got me.
What? When did that waistband guy counterattack?!
It was almost... at the same time...
That person's slash also flew...
That samurai zombie moves thanks to my shadow,
but he must truly have been
an extraordinary samurai when alive.
It is possible that those two have the same type of strength as swordsmen.
It means they possess the same destructive power.
This match won't take too long.
Prelude...
Au Fer!
Iron
A weapon breaking technique?!
Two Swords Style...
Flash!
Demon Bear!
Gavotte...
Bond Avant!
Forward Leap
Two Swords Style...
Sword Draw...
Castle Gate!
He got me!
The pillars broke!
H-Hold on a minute! Hey!
The whole floor is gonna collapse!
This is dangerous!
Hang on tight, we're outta here!
The ceiling is coming down!
Seventy-two Pound Cannon!
Phoenix of the Seventy-two Earthly Desires
Polka Continuation!
Weapons Left!
That was close!
Watch out! You'll fall!
I'm slipping!
How can they get a foothold?
If this keeps up, my blades will end up breaking...
The body and skill of this corpse is almost the same as the legendary samurai himself.
One Sword Style...
Flying Dragon...
Three Pace Hum...
Notch Slash!
Blaze!
Did his wound just ignite?
I lost.
Shuusui, the famous sword that once served a legendary samurai.
Shuusui: Clear Autumn Water
Surely this sword will be satisfied under your command.
Did that samurai just say something?
So that means...
w-what exactly?
It means...
that the match is over!
I've never seen a battle like this!
That samurai...
never fought against me seriously!
And some fight that was.
I feel sorry for...
giving this samurai body a complete defeat...
Having the feeling of shame is enough...
That's what makes a true swordsman in both body and soul.
I wish I could've met you when you were alive.
T-This is...!
It's back!
After five long years, my shadow is finally back!
I'll be taking the sword, but...
let's pretend this duel never happened,
samurai of Wano Country.
Well? How does it feel
to get captured by your own friends?
You failed to feed me salt with that weird ability!
He's strong...
Damn! I never thought Sanji would kick Robin!
This creature is no longer Sanji!
Who's this Sanji?
I'll kill you, damn bastard.
Unfortunately for you, they no longer have memories of being your friends.
Fresh zombies may have
remains of their former selves,
but now that the body and shadow have merged completely...
their humanity is gone for good.
They're my loyal zombies now!
And for a zombie, orders are absolute!
I'm almost glad that you've fallen this low, Hogback!
You once saved numerous human lives,
that's why I deeply admired you as a doctor,
even your zombie research.
Death...
it comes without warning...
Because of this, many things are left unsaid between those dead and those left behind...
Not for many years...
just a few minutes would be enough!
If there was a way to bring back the dead for even a brief moment...
even if it was an evil and heretical practice...
it would be hugely appreciated by those who were brought back!
That's why, when you spoke of raising the dead, I thought your words were...
worthy of a true doctor!
Fool! Why would I do that for strangers?!
They requested my aid for the same reason you admired me!
It was because I was a genius!
It was all about the money!
I didn't want to help all those patients who kept coming incessantly from all over the world!
"Please help my father!"
"Save my child!"
"Help my boyfriend!"
What a huge annoyance!
So troublesome.
I had to pay for the incompetence of all those pathetic doctors who couldn't even save a life.
Can you comprehend the trouble of being such a genius?!
Whether you respect me or not is up to you,
but the mere fact that I disappointed you is ridiculous.
If you can't stand me as a doctor because of your absurd ideals...
Then you're deceiving yourself, stupid reindeer!
You want to tell me what a doctor should be?!
I don't intend to tell you anything!
I don't think of you as a doctor anymore!
The same goes for those zombies!
They're just empty shells moving to your will!
They're not alive!
Don't play with life!
What a cruel statement.
You deny their livelihood despite seeing them move before your very eyes?!
Granting a new life to the dead is a true miracle!
How can you possibly deny the existence of this?!
Look!
Now then, lick the floor, Cindry.
Yes, Hogback-sama.
You saw that room, didn't you, Dr. Chopper?
That's my room.
All those were pictures of the stage actress Victoria Cindry, back when she was alive.
I completely fell in love with her.
Not only me, but men from the entire country, fell for such beauty.
It's fixed now, Doctor.
S-Sorry, I didn't mean to disturb my patient just to get my buttons sewn!
It's no problem!
A very popular yet unpretentious person...
devoted to her family,
She was kind to everyone... truly a wonderful woman.
but she...
rejected my proposal, the proposal of a doctor who had everything...
All because of that accursed fiancé of hers...!
And then...
Unbelievable news reached my ears...
Cindry... died in an accident.
My pain was indescribable...
I abandoned my work...
It was then that a huge man appeared before me...
My master, Gekko Moriah!
Dr. Hogback, lend me your power!
So we agreed that, in exchange for resurrecting Cindry with his miraculous ability, I would stay on this ship.
I stole her body...
and by doing so, I easily gained control over the actress Cindry!
Cindry-chan!
It would be best if all the plates disappear...
I didn't care about who the woman was inside her body...
As long as she had her beauty...
That's Cindry-chan's zombie!
I'm full of joy, and so is she.
I granted her a second opportunity to live as a human in this world!
How can you call this human?!
Make her stop!
A person with no connection between heart and body can't be called human!
If you're using soulless bodies...
you're just creating monsters!
You make people unhappy by creating those zombies!
Now that I'm aware of this, I won't let you off!
Don't talk to me about "life" with your limited medical skills, pirate-deer!
Cindry-chan, get rid of them!
I'll turn you both into marionettes!
You should be grateful, Dr. Chopper.
When you die, you'll become
the assistant of the person you admired!
Angular Edge Plate...
One!
Two!
Three!
Stop...
Bastard!
Chopper!
Don't look down on her just because she's a woman!
I've increased her strength for battle!
You don't have to listen to him!
I will kill you!
I feel bad for you. You're already dead.
How would the rest of your family feel if they knew about this?!
Let me... go!
Covered with patches, becoming just a mindless soldier...
Your relatives wouldn't bear to see you like this...
You damned... let me go!
The heart you were born with is dead now...
Your body moves under other people's wills...
What kind of life is that?!
You doubt your eyes?!
Accept it! This is the eternal dream of humans, revival of the dead!
The dead have been resurrected!
So if they can move, it's enough?!
Humans have more freedom than that!
You are not even treating them as humans!
Robin! Hurry and give her salt!
Dog-pen!
Jigoro!
Help Cindry!
Get rid of that nuisance!
I failed!
Chopper!
Three Swords Style...
One-hundred and Eight...
Pound Cannon!
Stop it, Zoro!
Doce Fleur!
Twelve Flowers
You nuisance...
Disappear!
Why'd you attack me too?!
Don't get in my way!
Now you made me angry!
That'd be you!
I received that order!
It was me!
Hey, what're you doing?!
Cut it out already!
You should be coopera-
Robin!
Such an amusing incident, don't you think?
All because of the order given to get rid of the nuisances.
Even with their memories erased...
It seems that the true nature of those two is to always be in conflict.
I'm shocked...
This seems like a tall tower.
Why don't you try telling us to jump off it?
What're you implying?!
That's exactly what I'll say!
Jump! Jump!
You two there, jump off!
Yes.
N-No, wait!
We'd rather not.
This is unforgivable!
You tricked me!
You're the lowest!
You're not human!
All the zombies will be purified once Luffy takes out Moriah...
I just want to pummel you, Hogback!
Cindry!
Buy me some time!
I'm getting out of here!
Why don't you answer?!
If you lose, I'll just give you another shadow!
Don't worry about dying!
My body...
won't move.
C-Cindry!
Translation & initial syncing, Vegapunk Fansubs
Syncing, Galaxy 9000, , Sync-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000, Feeso
Video editing, Sewil
Soundtracking, Halee
Raw provider, SOFCJ-Raws